<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dr. Mps</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="About" translatable="false">About Page</string>
    <string name="copy_right" translatable="false">Copyrights © %1$d</string>

    <string name="Challenger_Page_Text">"\"When you've got something to prove there's nothing greater than a challenge\"  \n\nEncouraging one and all to adopt sports as an integral part of routine to discipline oneself, to preserve to meet a goal, strengthen relation, instill self-confidence and above all release stress, anxiety and felicitate emotional stability and resilience.\n\n With great zeal, excitement and frolicsome atmosphere, Dr. MPS College organizes the \"Challengers\" Event. it is an annual event of 3 days in which students participate in various sports activities such as:\n
    ● Cricket
    ● Tug of War
    ● Throw Ball
    ● Table Tennis
    ● Basket Ball
    ● Badminton
    ● Volley Ball
    ● Kho-Kho
    ● Race
    ● Shot Put\n
        Sports here at Dr. MPS College is not only about competitions, it is also about having fun, Being physically active, learning the basics of sports and building coordination and teamwork and so to give the students an opportunity to display their talent, self-confidence, patience, zeal and sportsmanship.\n
        Through sports, students are able to build a wide range of abilities and skills such as leadership, teamwork, patience, self-reliance, trust and many more which facilitate the overall development of an individual. You become proactive on the court. Students also learn to manage time between their lectures, sports, and personal life.\n
        Sports is all about teamwork. Dr. MPS College encourages team sports which gives an individual a sense of identity and belonging to a group. Such sports encourage students to showcase their talent and communicate with their team members. It also helps to identify and hone their leadership skills which add values to their personality. Students not only stay fit and healthy by actively participating in sports, but they also learn effective ways to handle pressure in times of crisis.\n

    </string>

    <string name="itFest_page_text">
        IT-FEST is an initiative of Department of IT, Dr. MPS group to nurture the budding developers with technical skills and competitiveness to prove dexterous edge over others.
        \n\nIT-FEST "Technomania" is the finest platform for the ingenious minds to show their talents in the technical field and come together to put their skills to test. it is an assortment of various technological activities and literary events to honour the student\'s interests, competencies and technical skills. It aims to Motivating students to come together and share their enthusiasm and love for Technology.
        \n\n
        It provides an opportunity to students, where they can exhibit their technical competence, knowledge and skill sets required to be an effective developer. The two day program known for hosting a variety of events that include competitions, exhibitions, lectures as well as workshop. The fest has been conducted for the past 3 years and the number of participants last time was above 200.\n\n
        The IT fest is an annual program conducted by the students of BCA Department. There are more than three hundred students who spends their sweat and blood for success of the event. IT FEST creates awareness among students of IT and management about the practical exposure of the latest trends in Technology sector.

    </string>

    <string name="nationalcomference_text">
        Dr. MPS Group of Institution is a pioneer in the field of professional education in north India. It has taken meticulous and meaningful steps to build reservoirs of intellectual wealth and academic excellence to advance the educational, cultural, social and economic development of the wider community.\n\n
        As digital technologies are dramatically reshaping industry after industry, the corporate efforts to capture the benefits of these trends, which hold promise for deeper engagement with all the stakeholders.
        \n\nDigital innovation is getting increasingly interwoven into the very fabric of most businesses, marketers and societies, they strive to develop a digital vision and build new business models based on such opportunities, jump starting the organization\'s digital journey.
        \n\n
        National conference organized by Dr. MPS group on \"Configuring A Road Map for Transforming Businesses and Entrepreneurship under Digital Innovation\" help academicians and research scholars to interact with industrialists, entrepreneurs, corporate leaders, and gain deep insights into how corporate are building resilient sustainable business models, unlocking human potential using digital technology, and using AL-ML-IoT for developing tomorrow\'s products and services today and many other similar issues, through keynote deliberations, plenary technical sessions and case studies.\n
    </string>

    <string name="nss_page_text">
        The students of Dr. MPS group take part in NSS activities accompanied by the respective teachers.\n\n
        National Service Scheme (NSS) is an addition of activities in the higher education system of india with the aim of following students to develop their personally by providing community service while they are studying.
        \nThe scheme comes under the protection of the ministry of Youth Affairs \&amp; sports, Government of India Students under the NSS must put in 2 years of services along with their studies.
        \n\nUnder the scheme, Students must provide 120 hours of service every year as well as participate in at least one special camp programme. The main goal of the NSS is education via community service and community service via education. The two main activities of the scheme are special camping programme and regular activities.\n\n
        NSS is beneficial to both students as well as the society in various different means. it helps the student to grow individually and also as a group. it makes the student confident, develop leadership skills and gain different knowledge about different people from different walks of life.
        \n\n● To help students develop a democratic attitude and leadership qualities. Helping students share responsibilities and develop abilities towards group living.\n
        \n● To help develop civic and social responsibilities.\n
        \n● To help students understand their roles in the community. Helping students develop a capacity to handle emergency situations and natural disasters.\n
        \n● To Help gain skills for organising participation to the community.\n
        \n● To help students make use of their skills and knowledge to find practical solutions to community and individual problems.\n
        \n● To point out the problems and requirements of the community and help in solving them in case any problem arises. To know about the type of community they work in.\n
        \n● To Help students practice towards national interrogation and social harmony.\n

    </string>

    <string name="reminiscence_page_text">
        To be competent and successful in every sphere of life, a student needs many traits but the most crucial of them is confidence. To truly accept oneself, to take on challenges head-on, to outperform even under constant pressure and to face difficult situations and work continuously towards making oneself better.\n\n
        We at Dr. MPS college believe in bringing every student on stage for imbibing confidence among all and polishing every individual to make our students competent and successful in every sphere of life.\n\n
        \'Reminiscence\' is a celebration where students are provided with a big platform to exhibit heart throbbing and lively performances in front of thousands of people. it helps to remove their hesitation and stage fear and thus imbibes confidence and courage to face challenges. Students are fully charged, enthusiastic and full of zeal, creating an exciting atmosphere like on a large scale.\n

    </string>

    <string name="ranbhumi_page_text">
        At Dr. MPS college, Sports is an important part of the curriculum. We all need a break from classroom and lectures to rejuvenate and extracurricular activities are the best way to regain that energy and enhance our personalities. While academics play a significant role, sports-related activities are also important in shaping the personality and character of a student.\n\n
        With the same ideology, Dr. MPS College emphasizes on college sports activities and encourages its students to participate in various tournaments.\n\n
        \"Ranbhumi\", a Monthly Sports activity conducted by Dr. MPS College on every 4th saturday of the month, providing the students a platform where they realize their inner strength and the art of standing as a teams.\n\n
        Its a battleground for group of students, which helps them to learn the game of power and togetherness.\n\n
        With various sports activities such as:\n\n
        ● Cricket\n
        ● Volly Ball\n
        ● Football\n
        ● Badminton\n
        ● Table-Tennis\n\n
        students gain various skills and experience confidence which are helpful for developing their personality. it does not only aim t improve a students physical abilities but also instill a sense of good sportsmanship in them.\n\n
        Sports is all about teamwork, Dr. MPS College encourages team sports which gives an individual a sense of identity and belonging to a group. Such sports encourage students to showcase their talents and communicate with their members. it also helps them to identify and hone their leadership skills which add values to their personality.

    </string>

    <string name="college_fever_page_text">
        \"Collegefever.com\" is a cultural extravaganza organized by Dr. MPS College. The college takes immense joy and pleasure in conducting this culture blast on the 2nd saturday of every month providing student a platform to showcase their extraordinary talent.\n\n
        Saturday cultural blast \"Collegefever.com\" helps in witnessing the emotions of life through a wonderful splash of various events like:\n\n
        ● Solo Singing\n
        ● Comedy Nights\n
        ● Flash Back\n
        ● Mimicry\n
        ● Solo/Duet/trio Dance\n
        ● Poetry\n
        ● Karaoke\n
        ● Rap Up\n
        ● Skit\n
        ● Battle of Bands\n\n
        This cultural fest allows the students to connect to the resources available in the college and tap to their betterment and growth. This can only be possible by becoming involved in cultural events held in college. Taking part in these activities will allows the students to gauge their passions, their skills, their opportunities, Strengths and weakness. The knowledge of all these would help them decide their career after the college education.\n\n
        \"Collegefever.com\" is the flagship event of the Dr. MPS College and is open to students irrespective of their fields/specializations, thus providing a great opportunity to mingle and network with others from various walks of life.\n
    </string>

    <string name="nationalSeminar_page_test">
        National Seminar organized by department of Biotechnology of Dr. MPS Group of Institutions. The Main objective of this National Seminar is to promote the current researches and scientific acquaintances of Biotechnology and Agricultural Sciences for the sustainable development.\n\n
        National Seminar also provides a forum for healthy interaction on various aspects with eminent scientists, Industrialist, Entrepreneurs and Professors. It provide deep insights of biological sciences to the participants like:\n\n
        ● Innovations\n
        ● Creativity\n
        ● scientific temperament\n
        ● Skill Development\n
        \n
        It consist of various sessions including keynote speech, plenary and parallel technical sessions for vast interaction during the presentations of budding Scientists and Researchers on recent approaches.\n\n
        The Biotechnology Industry has expanded multifolds from last few decades with an ongoing increasing requirements of skilled professionals to accomplish higher researchers and industrial operations. Today, Indian Biotechnology sector comprises of more than 280 companies and 180 suppliers for generating revenue in different areas like Clinical Researches, Agricultural Sectors, Drug information etc. \n\nThe Central government also emphasizes Biotechnology Sector under the make in india program by providing financial and scientific support to the Research institutes and industries for better efforts to promote higher researchers and productivity. Enhancing understanding of Biological Sciences and inter disciplinary scientific approaches has resulted in major breakthrough of industrial products for the betterment of society. National Seminar is not only an opportunity to interact with eminent professionals from various disciplines and industries but also explore the possible ways for the collaboration between the institute and industries.
    </string>

    <string name="whymps_text1">\n
        ● More than 90% result in university Examinations.\n\n
        ● Excellent Placement Records.\n\n
        ● National Achievement award for Educational Excellence.\n\n
        ● Campus Partnership with renowned companies like Wipro, NIIT, Reliance etc.\n\n
        ● Education loan tie-up with HDFC Bank.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="whymps_text2">\n
        ● High Standards of Education.\n\n
        ● Highly Experienced Faculty.\n\n
        ● Modern Teaching Aids in classrooms.\n\n
        ● Multiple Skills Acquisition.\n\n
        ● Career Support through Effective Placement Assistance.\n\n
        ● Unique Learning Approach - EL - TLA (Experienced Learning – Training Learning Appraisal)\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="whymps_text3">\n
        ● Technology Enabled Classrooms\n\n
        ● Highly Enriched Library with Digital or E-Library\n\n
        ● Air-Conditioned Auditorium with Latest Presentation Aids\n\n
        ● Modern and Hitech Conference Hall\n\n
        ● Fully Equipped Laboratories of Biotech and Life Sciences\n\n
        ● Air-Conditioned and Highly advanced Computer Centre with 24 hours Internet Connectivity\n\n
        ● Seperate and Hygenic Hostels for Boys and Girls\n\n
        ● Transport Services on all Major Routes\n\n
        ● Air-Conditioned Cafeteria for Refreshment\n\n
        ● Outdoor and Indoor Sports Facilities\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="whymps_text4">\n
        ● Special Classroom Session for Communication Skills and Effective English Conversation\n\n
        ● Personality Development Programmes and Leadership Training\n\n
        ● Entrepreneurial Development Programmes\n\n
        ● Scholarships, Rewards and Recognitions for Outstanding Students\n\n
        ● Personal Monitoring of Each Student in Academics and Extra Curricular Activities\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="alumini_1">
        \"Finding the right path to success at the right time is really very important and for that way i had selected Dr. MPS College. The friendly environment, the systematic approach towards imparting education at Dr. MPS made me a competent individual. The wide range of activities and the support from Dr. MPS was really very helpful for my future. The faculties are really very kind and approachable when any need arises. In Dr. MPS we are trained for our placements and because of that i was placed in one of the reputed companies for my internship. Today, if I am in good position it\'s because of what I have learnt from Dr. MPS.\"
    </string>

    <string name="alumini_2">
        \"The past years in Dr. MPS passed by in swift immersing the students with knowledge, patience, and on top of all management abilities necessary to able to compete in the real world of business. It gave me a platform to push myself and to understand the potentials that was hidden inside me. These past three years not only helped me broaden my horizon on my knowledge on business and management but also helped me discover more about myself. I would like heartily thank all the teachers and staff in our college who are still there and who were formerly working as well, for helping me adjust to every situation the whole time when I was in Agra.\"
    </string>

    <string name="alumini_3">
        \"My experience at Dr. MPS College was different and has led me to explore and learn new things in terms of personal and professional aspects. The faculty at Dr. MPS focus on students\' career goals with proper guidance in selecting most suitable specialization based on one\'s strengths and passion. The pre-placements activities were highly effective for us to have a clear idea on facing interviews. The various co-curricular activities build confidence and leadership skills in me and helped me understand my potential and overcome my insecurities. The ambiance of the college has always been so positive and encourages to learn.\"
    </string>

    <string name="alumini_4">
        \"It was a wonderful experience at Dr. MPS with an excellent exposure provided across the various platforms. The faculties are very supportive and encourage students to push boundaries to rise above expectations. Dr. MPS targets for an overall development of every student, be it education, cultural awareness or practical exposure of business world like industrial exposure. The placement activities are pretty good and come with a training given on how to conduct oneself and face interviews confidently. The ambiance of the campus is very positive and the whole experience is very good and there is always support &amp; motivation from the management to pursue our dreams.\"
    </string>

    <string name="alumini_5">
        \"It was a great time, spent in Dr. MPS. It has very wonderful faculty and they are very cooperative. The relation between faculty and students is very cordial, which gave me an opportunity to excel further.The two years spent here was splendid and has helped me excel professionally as well as personally. Apart from academic, department offers various opportunities to enjoy our college days which was attracting us towards college most of the time.\"
    </string>

    <string name="alumini_6">
        \"It has been a great journey and an immense pleasure to have been nurtured during my undergraduate in Dr. MPS, 3 long years gave me a lot of exposure and opportunities to discover my hidden talents and excel in them. It has not only been the academics, but also the activities carried out with support of our respected Chairman, Director and Teachers. I\'m very happy to be a part of this amazing family of Dr. MPS.\"
    </string>

    <string name="vip_1">
        At the desk where I sit, I have learned one great truth. The answer for all our national problems- the answer for all the problems come to a single world. That word is “Education”. The objective of education is to prepare the young to educate themselves throughout their lives.\n\n
        Some people believe that holding on and hanging in there are signs of great strength however there are times when it takes much more strength to know when to let go and then do. You must learn day by day, year by year, to broaden your horizon. The more thing you love, the more you are interested in, the more you are indigent about, the more you have left when anything happens. The aim of education is the knowledge not of fact, but of values. In times of change, learner inherit the earth, while the learned find themselves beautifully equipped to deal with a world that no longer exists. I wish Dr. MPS Group of Institutions great future ahead.\n
    </string>

    <string name="vip_2">
        Education has been considered by all the greats in the history as the only way a person can be empowered in the true sense. And sensing this, every educational institute should be committed to contribute to the empowerment of one and all.\n\n
        Dr. MPS Group of Institutions is an infrastructural grandeur and educational hub, seeking new vistas of wisdom and knowledge. It stands distinctly apart from the other institution in as way that it offers a wide range of programs of study providing diversified options for professional qualification and at the same time personal growth as well. The college is making rapid strides to meet the challenges of higher education in modern times. Dr MPS provides an environment which is cordial and gives a great opportunity to the students to explore their latent talent in whatever field it may be whether it is in sports, music, dance or any other extracurricular activities.\n\n
        The college programs places great emphasis on employability and have already delivered industry-ready graduates equipped with the skills required for the competitive employment market. Dr MPS Group of Institutions throws its gate wide open to innovation and taking the risk to grow and learn. DR. MPS offers students value added courses that integrates the desire to challenge the self limits. An ambiance that is pitched in with high energy and fueled by the thought to “stretch yourself” be it individually, academically or socially. Opportunities are unlimited here and these opportunities are not merely mirages rather they are backed-up by an infrastructure that lends many conceivable opportunities.\n\n
        I take this opportunity to convey my best wishes and blessings to the teaching faculty, administrative staff and college management for their instituted support in all their future endeavour that helps the students to realize their cherished goal.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="vip_3">
        We are leading to a future where rapidly changing technologies and global challenges will pose a fierce competition to of us. The information and technology are becoming increasingly accessible to everyone. Only those individuals with exceptional potential and skill will survive. In this crucial battle of life, knowledge is also a predominant weapon to win.\n\n
        If learning is empowered with the best of human virtues and values, the life will automatically transcend time. What is important is the fusion of Education and Personality to enhance endurance and potential. Education and degrees are sold every where, but are they able to fulfill our dreams? If all the education we have achieved is unable to give us a dignified and successful life, it is useless.\n\n
        Everyone of us dreams of a career not only to earn livelihood but also to get social status and prosperity. It is a destination which begins the journey of our life. We are constantly working to develop an ethical system of education which makes you exceptional to realize your potential and transformthem into reality. We don’t have to be genius, or an exceptional person to be successful in life. An average person with faith in himself, motivated and self driven can easily make a wonderful career. Our unique system focused on your personality, communication skills and leadership qualities.\n\n
        Come and discover yourself a word of opportunities, safe destination for smart careers.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="vip_4">
        I am delighted that you are considering “Dr. MPS Group College of Business Studies &amp; Hotel Management “ for your higher education in pursuit of your career growth. I extend you a warm welcome and assure you that we will not leave any stone unturned for your success in your endeavours.\n\n

        Here we impart value education along with many opportunities to hone your 4 skills and nurture your talent. The College has a team of highly qualified and dedicated teachers and professionals to guide and mentor the students. A community of inspired faculty and talented students grow together to shape a dynamic energy field.\n\n

        We look for students who have seriousness of purpose both in the classroom and outside learning at this college is viewed as an experience, which is not only to gain knowledge, but also about building character and life skills, involving a holistic approach to make you an achiever in the competitive world that you will step in after college life.\n\n

        The backbone of the college is its dedicated faculty, an efficient administrative staff and a strong supportive management. The mind blowing world class infrastructure, a wonderful educational environment and ambitious expansion plans defines our unique class and culture. We are always dedicated to provide all the resources and impetus to the College for its continuous expansion and improvement.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="vip_5">
        Dear Students, \n\n

        Human capital is a driver for technological innovation and economic growth of the country. Education is the most important investment in the field of human resource development which is necessary to build this human capital. The youth is the future of any country and in India where fifty percent of population is young it becomes all the more important to emphasize on quality based professional education to ensure the real growth of the nation. Dr MPS Group is committed for creating an ambience for nurturing innovation, creativity and excellence in our students along with a sense of strong values and ethics in a friendly and open culture. We strongly support high quality academic inputs to all our students and try to bring out the best of their persona so that they will be self driven on the path of success.\n\n

        We believe that a mix of competent, enlightened and dedicated faculty, a meticulously designed curriculum and an optimum infrastructure is going to ensure that our students inculcate result driven attitude, professional orientation, discipline and energetic approach. We aim to promote equality, freedom with accountability and an uncompromising jest for performance along with the social responsibility. Professional learning is about dealing with business realities. Therefore, our pedagogy involves not only class room teaching but also working on live projects, along with regular interactions with the corporate world. We have strong industry interface to benefit in terms of Guest Lectures, Seminars/Workshops, Industry Visits, Summer Internship and Final Placements. We ensure that our students are also provided elaborate inputs on creativity, communication skill and personality development, ensuring all round holistic development. The curriculum process has been carefully planned to enable students to prove their worth on any front and accomplish their academic, personal and professional ambitions\n\n

        It gives me immense satisfaction when I say that we spare no efforts in giving the very best to our students and preparing them to take the world in their stride. I take this opportunity to congratulate and accord a warm welcome to the journey that embarks on achieving your cherished dreams and ambitions. My colleagues and I would be delighted to welcome you to be part of our students’ fraternity to experience a superior professionalism on the path that will immensely help you to attain your career objectives .\n\n
    </string>
</resources>